The gold or the grave. The young widow could lead them to either.
The Train Robbers is a western, action film directed by Burt Kennedy.
A gunhand named Lane is hired by a widow, Mrs.
Lowe, to find gold stolen by her husband so that
she may return it and start fresh.
Lane, played by John Wayne.
Mrs. Lowe, played by Ann-Margret.
Grady, played by Rod Taylor.
Jesse, played by Ben Johnson.
Calhoun, played by Christopher George.
Ben Young, played by Bobby Vinton.
The Train Robbers is a 1973 American Western film written and directed by Burt Kennedy and
starring John Wayne, Ann-Margret, Rod Taylor, Ben Johnson, and Ricardo Montalbán.
Filming took place in Sierra de Órganos National Park
in the town of Sombrerete, Mexico.
Two brief scenes take place in the square that was used for the
final shootout in Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid.
Kennedy called the film one of his only "really good"
films after Support Your Local Sheriff.
The film explores themes of gold, widow, hired gun.